Once you wish, your soul is bound.
The Final Wish is a horror film directed by Timothy Woodward Jr..
Following the passing of his father, Aaron Hammond returns to his hometown to
help his devastated mother and to confront his past demons.
Sifting through his father’s belongings, Aaron comes upon a
mysterious item that is far more than it seems.
Kate Hammond, played by Lin Shaye.
Aaron Hammond, played by Michael Welch.
Lisa, played by Melissa Bolona.
Lynette, played by Spencer Locke.
Colin, played by Tony Todd.
Derek, played by Kaiwi Lyman.
The Final Wish is a 2018 mystery-horror film directed by Timothy Woodward Jr., written by Jeffrey Reddick
(also co-producer), William Halfon and Jonathan Doyle, and starring Lin Shaye and Michael Welch.
Distributed by Cinedigm Entertainment Group, The Final Wish was released on
October 17, 2018 at the Screamfest Horror Film Festival.
The film explores themes of mother, death of
father, jinn, wishes come true, grim.
The tone is dark and intense.